Guide to the American Dance Festival Photographic Materials Collection, circa 1930-2008
American Dance Festival Archives
- Company and Biographical, circa 1930-2008
  - Taylor 2, 1995, (35 mm slides, 35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 33)
  - Taylor, Bruce, 1980, (35 mm slides) (Box 33)
  - Taylor, Paul, 1961-1971, undated, (prints) (Box 18)
  - Taylor, Paul, 1979, (35 mm slides) (Box 33)
  - Taylor, Paul, 1983, (prints) (Box 18)
  - Taylor, Paul, 1983, (35 mm slides, 35 mm b&w contact sheets) (Box 33)
  - Taylor, Paul, 1992, 1995, (prints) (Box 18)
  - Taylor, Paul, 1996-1997, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 33)
  - Taylor, Paul, 1997, 1999, (prints) (Box 18)
  - Taylor, Paul, 1999, (35 mm color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 33)
  - Taylor, Paul, Headshots, 1974, undated, (prints) (Box 18)
  - Taylor, Paul Taylor Dance Company, 1956-1964, (prints) (Box 18)
  - Taylor, Paul Taylor Dance Company, 1965, (prints) (Box 18)
  - Taylor, Paul Taylor Dance Company, 1965, (prints) (Box OS1)
  - Taylor, Paul Taylor Dance Company, 1965, undated, (prints) (Box OS1)
  - Taylor, Paul Taylor Dance Company, 1966-1969, (prints) (Box 18)
  - Taylor, Paul Taylor Dance Company, 1971-1978, (prints) (Box 18)
  - Taylor, Paul Taylor Dance Company, 1979, undated, (35 mm slides) (Box 33)
  - Taylor, Paul Taylor Dance Company, 1985-1988, 1992-1993, (prints) (Box 18)
  - Taylor, Paul Taylor Dance Company, 1994, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 33)
  - Taylor, Paul Taylor Dance Company, 1995, (35 mm slides, 35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 33)
  - Taylor, Paul Taylor Dance Company, 1995-1997, (prints) (Box 18)
  - Taylor, Paul Taylor Dance Company, 1996, (35 mm slides, 35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 33)
  - Taylor, Paul Taylor Dance Company, 1997, (35 mm slides, 35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 33)
  - Taylor, Paul Taylor Dance Company, 1998, (35 mm slides, 35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 33)
  - Taylor, Paul Taylor Dance Company, 1999, (35 mm color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 33)
  - Taylor, Paul Taylor Dance Company, 1999, (prints) (Box 18)
  - Taylor, Paul Taylor Dance Company, 2000, (35 mm slides, 35 mm color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 33)
  - Taylor, Paul Taylor Dance Company, 2001, (35 mm color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 33)
  - Taylor, Paul Taylor Dance Company, 2001-2002, (prints) (Box 18)
  - Taylor, Paul Taylor Dance Company, 2002, (35 mm color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 33)
  - Taylor, Paul Taylor Dance Company, Publicity, 1974, (prints) (Box 18)
  - Taylor, Paul Taylor Dance Company, Publicity, 1979-1983, (prints) (Box 18)
  - Taylor, Paul Taylor Dance Company, Publicity, 2000, (prints) (Box 18)
  - Taylor, Paul Taylor Dance Company, Publicity, circa 1990-1999, (prints) (Box 18)
  - Taylor, Paul Taylor Dance Company, Publicity, circa 1990-1999, (prints) (Box 18)
  - Taylor, Paul Taylor Dance Company, undated, (prints) (Box 18)
  - Taylor, Paul Taylor Dance Company, undated, (prints) (Box 18)
  - Taylor, Paul Taylor Dance Company, undated, (8 x 10 b&w negatives, 4 x 5 b&w negatives) (Box 33)
  - Taylor, Paul Taylor Dance Company Members, undated, (prints) (Box 18)
  - Taylor, Robin Harris Taylor and Dancers, undated, (prints) (Box 18)
  - Teeters, Clarence, 1986, 1987, (prints) (Box 19)
  - Teker, Aydin, 1993, (prints) (Box 19)
  - Teker, Aydin, 1993, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 33)
  - Telizzi, Alfred, undated, (prints) (Box 19)
  - Tetley, Glen, circa 1962, (prints) (Box 19)
  - Tetley, Glen Tetley Dance Company, circa 1962, (prints) (Box 19)
  - Tharp, Twyla, 1990, 2000, undated, (prints) (Box 19)
  - Tharp, Twyla, 1999-2000, (35 mm color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 33)
  - Tharp, Twyla, undated, (8 x 10 b&w negatives) (Box 33)
  - Tharp, Twyla Tharp Dance, 1980, 1985, undated, (prints) (Box 19)
  - Tharp, Twyla Tharp Dance, 2000, (prints) (Box 19)
  - Tharp, Twyla Tharp Dance, 2000, (35 mm color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 33)
  - Tharp!, 1999, (35 mm color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 33)
  - Tharp!, 1999, undated, (prints) (Box 19)
  - Theatre Provincial Dances, 1994, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 33)
  - Theatre Provincial Dances, circa 1993, (prints) (Box 19)
  - Thingsezisee'm Dance/Theatre, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 33)
  - Thingsezise'm, 1998, (prints) (Box 19)
  - Thomas, Marnie, undated, (prints) (Box 19)
  - Thomason, Helgi, undated, (prints) (Box 19)
  - Tosti, Ken, 1996, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 33)
  - Tosti, Ken, 1996, undated, (prints) (Box 19)
  - Traditional Dances of North Carolina, 1978, circa 1979, (prints) (Box 19)
  - Trovillion, Nancy, 1988, (prints) (Box 19)
  - Troy, Ellen, undated, (prints) (Box 19)
  - Truss, Tom, 1994, (35 mm b&w contact sheet) (Box 33)
  - Truss, Tom, 1995, (35 mm color negatives) (Box 33)
  - Truss, Tom and Amie Dowling, 1993, 1995, (prints) (Box 19)
  - Uchizono, Donna, 1990, (prints) (Box 19)
  - Unidentified, 1997, undated, (35 mm slides, 35 mm color negatives and contact sheets, 8 x 10 b&w negatives) (Box 33)
  - Unzveta, Silvia, 1990, (prints) (Box 19)
  - Urban Bush Women, 1998, (prints) (Box 19)
  - Urban Bush Women, 1998, (35 mm slides, 35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 33)
  - Utah Repertory Dance Theatre, 1992, (prints) (Box 19)
  - Valencia, Monica, 1992, (prints) (Box 19)
  - Varone, Doug, 1990, 2002, (prints) (Box 19)
  - Varone, Doug, 2000, (prints) (Box 19)
  - Varone, Doug, 2002, (35 mm color negatives) (Box 33)
  - Varone, Doug Varone and Dancers, 1990, (prints) (Box 19)
  - Varone, Doug Varone and Dancers, 1999-2000, (35 mm slides, 35 mm color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 33)
  - Varone, Doug Varone and Dancers, 2000, (prints) (Box 19)
  - Venable, Lucy, 1964, (35 mm slides) (Box 33)
  - Venable, Lucy, undated, (prints) (Box 19)
  - Vernon, Charlie, 1982, (prints) (Box 19)
  - Vernon, Charlie Vernon Performance Company, 1982, (prints) (Box 19)
  - Villamil, Jaclynn, 1994, undated, (prints) (Box 19)
  - Villamil, Jaclynn, 1997, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 33)
  - Villamil, Jaclynn, undated, (8 x 10 b&w negative) (Box 33)
  - Villela, Edward, undated, (prints) (Box 19)
  - Von Bardeleben, Armgordvon, 1985, 1988, undated, (prints) (Box 19)
  - Vrouna, Bruce, circa 1980-1981, (prints) (Box 19)
  - Wagoner, Dan, undated, (prints) (Box 19)
  - Ward, Cathy, circa 1984, (prints) (Box 19)
  - Waring, James, undated, (prints) (Box 19)
  - Watanabe, June, circa 1986-1988, (prints) (Box 19)
  - Weidman, Charles, 1940, circa 1951, 1957, undated, (prints) (Box 19)
  - Weidman, Charles, undated, (prints) (Box OS1)
  - Weidman, Charles Weidman and Group, 1964, undated, (prints) (Box 19)
  - Weinzweig, Meira, 1988, (prints) (Box 19)
  - Wei-Win, Xue, 1985, (prints) (Box 19)
  - Welliver, Gwen, 2000, (prints) (Box 19)
  - Welliver, Gwen, 2000, (35 mm color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 33)
  - Wilemon, Ken, undated, (prints) (Box 19)
  - Williams, Jim, 1989, (prints) (Box 19)
  - Williamson, Liz, undated, (prints) (Box 19)
  - Willson, John, 1983, (prints) (Box 19)
  - Winter, Ethel, 1948, (prints) (Box 19)
  - Wolenski, Chester, undated, (prints) (Box 19)
  - Wolfangle, Karla, 1998, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 33)
  - Wood, David, circa 1957, (prints) (Box 19)
  - Wood, David, circa 1965, (2 1/4 b&w contact sheets, 35 mm b&w contact sheets) (Box 33)
  - Woodcock, Jude, 2000, (prints) (Box 19)
  - Woodcock, Jude, 2000, (35 mm color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 33)
  - Woods, Andrea, 2000, (35 mm color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 33)
  - Woods, Andrea, 2000,2002, (prints) (Box 19)
  - Woods, Phil, circa 1996, (prints) (Box 19)
  - Xing, Jin, 1989, (prints) (Box 19)
  - Yang, Ming-Lung, 2000, (prints) (Box 19)
  - Yang, Ming-Lung, undated, (35 mm color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 33)
  - Yearby, Marlies, 1992, (prints) (Box 19)
  - Yearby, Marlies, 2000, (prints) (Box 19)
  - Yearby, Marlies, 2000, (35 mm color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 33)
  - Yuriko, circa 1965, (35 mm slides) (Box 33)
  - Zambrano, David, 1997, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 33)
  - Zarek, Sonja, undated, (prints) (Box 19)
  - Zhong, Li Han and Ma Bo (ICCP), 1999, (prints) (Box 19)
  - Zhong, Li Han and Ma Bo (ICCP), 1999, (35 mm color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 33)
  - Zollar, Jawole Willa Jo, 1998, (prints) (Box 19)
- Bennington College, circa 1930-1942
  The Bennington College series contains images of the campus, faculty, staff, classes, and showings from the Bennington School of Dance from the early 1930s until 1942.
  - Campus, circa 1930-1940, (prints) (Box 20)
  - Campus, Faculty, Staff, 1934-1942, (4 x 5 b&w negatives) (Box 34)
  - Classes and Showings, Graham Technique, 1934-1942, (prints) (Box 20)
  - Classes and Showings, Graham Technique, circa 1930, (prints) (Box 20)
  - Classes and Showings, Individuals, unidentified, 1938-1942, (prints) (Box 20)
  - Classes and Showings, Jose Limon, 1938-1942, (prints) (Box 20)
  - Classes and Showings, Outdoor Group, circa 1930, (prints) (Box 20)
  - Classes and Showings, Outdoor, circa 1930, (prints) (Box 20)
  - Classes and Showings, undated, (8 x 10 b&w negative) (Box 34)
  - Faculty and Staff, album, circa 1930-1940, (prints) (Box 20)
  - Faculty and Staff, circa 1930-1940, (prints) (Box 20)
  - Faculty and Staff, undated, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 34)
  - Faculty, Staff, and Students, 1934, (prints) (Box OS2)
  - Faculty, Staff, and Students, Album, undated, (prints) (Box OS2)
- Connecticut College, 1950-1977
  The Connecticut College series contains images of campus, faculty, staff, students, classes, showings, and other events at the American Dance Festival during its tenure at Connecticut College, which ended in 1977.
  - Audiences, undated, (prints) (Box 20)
  - Auditions, 1965, (2 1/4 b&w contact sheet) (Box 34)
  - Auditions, undated, (prints) (Box 20)
  - Campus, 1961-1965, (35 mm slides) (Box 34)
  - Campus, 1966-1970, (35 mm slides) (Box 34)
  - Campus, 1971-1972, (35 mm slides) (Box 34)
  - Campus, 1973, (35 mm slides) (Box 34)
  - Campus, undated, (prints) (Box 20)
  - Classes and Showings, 1965, (2 1/4 b&w contact sheets, 35 mm b&w contact sheets, 35 mm slides) (Box 34)
  - Classes and Showings, 1971, (35 mm b&w contact sheets) (Box 34)
  - Classes and Showings, 1972, (35 mm b&w contact sheets) (Box 34)
  - Classes and Showings, Children, circa 1965, (2 1/4 b&w contact sheets) (Box 34)
  - Classes and Showings, Children, Photographer: Biscuti, Philip, Sanders, Dora, and Urwillwer, Jack, (prints) (Box 21)
  - Classes and Showings, Children, Photographer: Moore, Patricia Jean, undated, (prints) (Box 21)
  - Classes and Showings, Children, Photographer: unidentified, undated, (prints) (Box 21)
  - Classes and Showings, Children, undated, (prints) (Box OS2)
  - Classes and Showings, Horst, Louis, undated, (prints) (Box 21)
  - Classes and Showings, Labanotation, undated, (prints) (Box 21)
  - Classes and Showings, Limon, Jose, undated, (2 1/4 b&w contact sheets) (Box 34)
  - Classes and Showings, Perez, Rudy, 1972, (prints) (Box 21)
  - Classes and Showings, Photographer: Arnold, (prints) (Box OS2)
  - Classes and Showings, Photographer: Arnold, David L., undated, (prints) (Box 20)
  - Classes and Showings, Photographer: Biscuti, (prints) (Box OS2)
  - Classes and Showings, Photographer: Biscuti, Philip A., Outdoor, undated, (prints) (Box 20)
  - Classes and Showings, Photographer: Biscuti, Philip A., undated, (prints) (Box 20)
  - Classes and Showings, Photographer: Melcer, Fannie Helen, undated, (prints) (Box 20)
  - Classes and Showings, Photographer: Moore, Patricia Jean, undated, (prints) (Box 20)
  - Classes and Showings, Photographer: Sanders, Dora and Swahn, Harold, undated, (prints) (Box 21)
  - Classes and Showings, Photographer: unidentified, (prints) (Box OS2)
  - Classes and Showings, Photographer: unidentified, 1950, (prints) (Box 21)
  - Classes and Showings, Photographer: unidentified, class instructor or subject identified, undated, (prints) (Box 21)
  - Classes and Showings, Photographer: unidentified, outdoor classes and close-ups of individuals, undated, (prints) (Box 21)
  - Classes and Showings, Photographer: unidentified, undated, (prints) (Box 21)
  - Classes and Showings, undated (2 folders), (2 1/4 b&w negatives, 2 1/4 b&w contact sheets, 35 mm b&w contact sheets, 8 x 10 b&w negatives, 35 mm slide) (Box 34)
  - Community Outreach, circa 1974, (35 mm b&w contact sheets) (Box 34)
  - Council on the Arts, undated, (2 1/4 b&w negatives) (Box 34)
  - Dance Advance, 1962, (prints) (Box 21)
  - Dance Advance, 1964, (35 mm slides) (Box 34)
  - Dance Advance, 1964, 1966, 1968, (prints) (Box 21)
  - Dance-Television Workshop, 1974, (35 mm b&w contact sheets) (Box 34)
  - Dancing at Nursery School, 1967, (2 1/4 b&w negatives) (Box 34)
  - Faculty and Staff, 1965, 1968, undated, (2 1/4 b&w contact sheets, 35 mm b&w contact sheets) (Box 34)
  - Faculty and Staff, undated, (prints) (Box 21)
  - Instant Music, Rhoderian Women, 1964, (35 mm slides) (Box 34)
  - International, undated, (35 mm b&w contact sheets) (Box 34)
  - Parties, undated, (2 1/4 b&w contact sheet, 35 mm b&w contact sheet) (Box 34)
  - Reception, 1969-1975, (prints) (Box 21)
  - Slide Presentation, 1966, (35 mm slides) (Box 39)
  - Students, 1964-1967, (2 1/4 b&w contact sheets, 35 mm b&w contact sheets) (Box 34)
  - Students, 1972, (35 mm contact sheets) (Box 34)
  - Students, International, 1960, (prints) (Box 21)
  - Students, undated, (prints) (Box 21)
  - Workshops, circa 1977, (prints) (Box 21)
  - Unidentified Performances, undated, (35 mm slide, 2 1/4 b&w contact sheets, 35 mm b&w contact sheets) (Box 34)
  - Unidentified, undated, (35 mm b&w contact sheets, 8 x 10 b&w negatives) (Box 34)
  - Duplicates, undated, (35 mm slides) (Box 34)
- Duke University, 1978-2008
  The Duke University series contains images of campus, faculty, staff, students, classes, showings, and other events associated with the American Dance Festival during its time at Duke University.
  - ADF China, 1988, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets, 35 mm color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 35)
  - ADF Korea, 1992, (8 x 10 b&w negatives) (Box 35)
  - ADF Korea, 1996, (prints) (Box 22)
  - ADF on Tour, circa 1993, (prints) (Box 22)
  - ADF on Tour, Minneapolis, 1995, (prints) (Box 22)
  - ADF Russia III, 2000, (prints) (Box 22)
  - ADF Tokyo, 1986, (prints) (Box 22)
  - Auditions, 1978, 1979, undated, (35 mm slides, 35 mm b&w contact sheets) (Box 35)
  - Balasaraswati/Beinecke Award, 1991-1993, (prints) (Box 22)
  - Balasaraswati/Beinecke Award, 1993-1994 (Betty Jones, Bella Lewitsky), (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 35)
  - Balasaraswati/Beinecke Award, 1995-1996 (Ethel Butler, Anna Halprin), (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 35)
  - Balasaraswati/Beinecke Award, 1997-1998 (McKayle, Schonberg, Mattox, Koner), (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 35)
  - Balasaraswati/Beinecke Award, 1999, 2002, (prints) (Box 22)
  - Balasaraswati/Beinecke Award, 1999-2000, (35 mm color negatives and contact sheets, 2 1/4 color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 35)
  - Balasaraswati/Beinecke Award, 2001 (Pearl Lang), (35 mm color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 35)
  - Balasaraswati/Beinecke Award, 2002 (Martha Myers), (35 mm color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 35)
  - Cakewalk Contest, 1980, (35 mm slides) (Box 35)
  - Cakewalk Contest, 1982, (prints) (Box 22)
  - Capezio Dance Award, 1996, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 35)
  - Classes and Showings, 1978-1979, (35 mm slides, 35 mm b&w contact sheets) (Box 35)
  - Classes and Showings, 1980, (35 mm slides) (Box 35)
  - Classes and Showings, 1980-1983, (prints) (Box 22)
  - Classes and Showings, 1981, (35 mm slides) (Box 35)
  - Classes and Showings, 1983, (35 mm slides, 35 mm b&w contact sheets) (Box 35)
  - Classes and Showings, 1984, 1986, (prints) (Box OS2)
  - Classes and Showings, 1984-1986, undated, (8 x 10 b&w negative) (Box 35)
  - Classes and Showings, 1985, (prints) (Box 22)
  - Classes and Showings, 1986-1988, (prints) (Box 22)
  - Classes and Showings, 1987, (35 mm slides) (Box 35)
  - Classes and Showings, 1993-1994, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 35)
  - Classes and Showings, 1994, (prints) (Box 22)
  - Classes and Showings, 1995, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 35)
  - Classes and Showings, 1995-1996, (prints) (Box 22)
  - Classes and Showings, 1996, (35 mm slides, 35 mm b&w contact sheets) (Box 35)
  - Classes and Showings, 1997, (prints) (Box 22)
  - Classes and Showings, 1997, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 35)
  - Classes and Showings, 1998-1999, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets, 35 mm color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 35)
  - Classes and Showings, 1999, (prints) (Box 22)
  - Classes and Showings, 2000, (prints) (Box 22)
  - Classes and Showings, 2000, (35 mm color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 35)
  - Classes and Showings, 2001, (prints) (Box 22)
  - Classes and Showings, 2001, (35 mm color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 35)
  - Classes and Showings, 2002, (prints) (Box 22)
  - Classes and Showings, 2002, (35 mm color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 35)
  - Classes and Showings, 2003, (prints) (Box 22)
  - Classes and Showings, 2005, (prints) (Box 22)
  - Classes and Showings, International Students, 1994, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 35)
  - Classes and Showings, International Students, 1996, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 35)
  - Classes and Showings, Ruby Shang, 1985-1986, (prints) (Box 22)
  - Classes and Showings, Tap/Flamenco, 1992, (prints) (Box 22)
  - Classes and Showings, undated, (prints) (Box 22)
  - Classes and Showings, undated, (8 x 10 b&w negatives, 4 x 5 b&w negatives, 35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 35)
  - Color Treated Slides, 1979, (35 mm slides) (Box 35)
  - Community Crossover, 1994, (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 35)
  - Community Crossover, 1996, (35 mm slides) (Box 35)
  - Community Crossover, 1999, (35 mm color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 35)
  - Community Crossover, 1999-2001, (prints) (Box 23)
  - Community Crossover, 2001, (35 mm color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 35)
  - Community Outreach, 1993, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 35)
  - Community Outreach, 1999 (5 folders), (prints) (Box 23)
  - Community Outreach, undated, (prints) (Box 23)
  - Community Outreach Residency Workshop, 2002, (prints) (Box 23)
  - Community Outreach Residency Workshop, 2003, (prints) (Box 23)
  - Critics Conference, 1979, (35 mm slides) (Box 35)
  - Dance Cultural Study Team: People's Republic of China, 1980, (prints) (Box 23)
  - Dance Therapy, 1993, (prints) (Box 23)
  - Dance Therapy, 1993-1994, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 36)
  - Dance Town Hall, 1979-1980, (35 mm slides) (Box 36)
  - Dance Town Hall, 1979-1981 (2 folders), (prints) (Box 23)
  - Dance Town Hall, 1980, (prints) (Box 23)
  - Dance Update (Workshop for Professionals), 1995, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 36)
  - Dance/Television Workshop, 1979, (35 mm slides) (Box 36)
  - Dance/Television Workshop, 1980, (35 mm slides) (Box 36)
  - Emerging Generation, 1981, 2001, (prints) (Box 23)
  - Emerging Generation, 2001, (35 mm color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 36)
  - Exhibit: Landmarks and Landscapers, 2000, (35 mm color negatives) (Box 36)
  - Exhibits, 1984 (2 folders), (prints) (Box 23)
  - Exhibits, 1998, (prints) (Box 23)
  - Exhibits, 2000, (prints) (Box 23)
  - Facilities, 715 Broad St., 1997, (prints) (Box 23)
  - Facilities, 715 Broad St., undated, (35 mm color negatives) (Box 36)
  - Facilities, Baldwin Auditorium, 1980, 1985, (35 mm slides) (Box 36)
  - Facilities, East Campus, 1979, (35 mm slides) (Box 36)
  - Facilities, Page Auditorium, 1979-1980, 1985, undated, (35 mm slides) (Box 36)
  - Facilities, Page Auditorium, 1984-1988, undated, (prints) (Box 23)
  - Faculty and Staff, 1978, (prints) (Box 23)
  - Faculty and Staff, 1979, (35 mm slides) (Box 36)
  - Faculty and Staff, 1980, 1984, (35 mm slides, 2 1/4 b&w contact sheet) (Box 36)
  - Faculty and Staff, 1985-1987, (prints) (Box 23)
  - Faculty and Staff, 1989-1990, (prints) (Box 23)
  - Faculty and Staff, 1992-1994, (prints) (Box 23)
  - Faculty and Staff, 1993-1994, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets, 2 1/4 b&w contact sheets) (Box 36)
  - Faculty and Staff, 1995-1996, (35 mm b&w negatives, 2 1/4 b&w negatives) (Box 36)
  - Faculty and Staff, 1996-1998, (prints) (Box 23)
  - Faculty and Staff, 1997-1998, (2 1/4 b&w negatives) (Box 36)
  - Faculty and Staff, 1999, (2 1/4 color negatives and contact sheet) (Box 36)
  - Faculty and Staff, 2000-2001, (2 1/4 color negatives and contact sheet) (Box 36)
  - Faculty and Staff, 2000-2002, (prints) (Box 23)
  - Faculty and Staff, 2002, (35 mm color negatives) (Box 36)
  - Faculty and Staff, circa 1980, (prints) (Box OS2)
  - Faculty and Staff, circa 1980, (35 mm b&w contact sheets, 35 mm color negatives) (Box 36)
  - Faculty and Staff, circa 1983, (prints) (Box 23)
  - Faculty Concert, 1979, 1980, (35 mm slides) (Box 36)
  - Faculty Concert, 2001, (35 mm color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 36)
  - Festival Africa, 1982-1983, (35 mm slides, 35 mm b&w contact sheets) (Box 36)
  - Fiftieth Anniversary, 1984, (35 mm color negatives, 4 x 5 b&w negative) (Box 36)
  - Gala, 25th Anniversary, 2002, (35 mm color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 36)
  - Governor's Reception, 1979, (35 mm slides) (Box 36)
  - Humanities Panel, 1994, (prints) (Box 23)
  - International Choreographers (ICCPs and ICWs), 1984-1985, (prints) (Box 24)
  - International Choreographers (ICCPs and ICWs), 1988-1990, (prints) (Box 24)
  - International Choreographers (ICCPs and ICWs), 1992-1993, (prints) (Box 24)
  - International Choreographers (ICCPs and ICWs), 1994-1995, (prints) (Box 24)
  - International Choreographers (ICCPs and ICWs), 1996-1997, (prints) (Box 24)
  - International Choreographers (ICCPs and ICWs), 1998-1999, (prints) (Box 24)
  - International Choreographers (ICCPs and ICWs), 2000, (prints) (Box 24)
  - International Choreographers (ICCPs and ICWs), undated, (prints) (Box 24)
  - International Choreographers (ICCPs), 1994, (35 mm slides) (Box 36)
  - International Choreographers in Residence (ICR), 1995, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 36)
  - International Choreographers in Residence (ICR), 1998, (35 mm b&w contact sheet) (Box 36)
  - International Choreographers in Residence (ICR), 2001, (35 mm color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 36)
  - International Choreographers in Residence (ICR), 2002, (35 mm color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 36)
  - International Choreographers Workshop (ICW), 1993, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 36)
  - International Dance Critics Conference (IDCC), 1993-1994, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 36)
  - International Dance Critics Conference, 1990, 1993-1994, (prints) (Box 24)
  - International Linkages Program, Guandong, China, circa 1987-1990 (2 folders), (prints) (Box 24)
  - Looking at Dance, 1995, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 36)
  - Looking at Dance, 1997, 1999-2001, (prints) (Box 24)
  - Looking at Dance, 1997-998, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 36)
  - Looking at Dance, 1999, (35 mm color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 36)
  - Looking at Dance, 2000-2001, (35 mm color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 36)
  - MAD (Music and Dance), 1979-1980, (35 mm slides) (Box 36)
  - Massage Therapy, 1983, (prints) (Box 24)
  - Other Events, 1978, 1980, (35 mm slides) (Box 37)
  - Other Events, AADF Charter Meeting, 1979, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 37)